Hey everyone, welcome to today's video. I'm going to show you the complete royal gold collection from Shashkufit.
And it's basically the perfect time to show you the royal gold stuff because it's Christmas soon.
So you either know what to wear for your Christmas festivities or what to put under the Christmas tree.
And I have several leggings, pants, catsuit, shaper tops with booty lift effects, the Shashkufit pants you've seen before here.
I'm going to link the video and I hope you enjoyed this one. Let's start with the classic combination
pants and you can already tell that they're really comfy and thick and have like cozy lining here and
the shape at top
Okay, so we have really high race
pants here with the zipper
and
from behind the bum push-up effect with the
pockets that are no real pockets but they make my booty look great the top is almost like
shapewear because it makes really nice boobies with a great push-up effect i'm not wearing a
bra underneath so this is a really good fit and you can open the middle zipper but the other ones
are like for decoration or if you want to yeah make the top bit more loose because if you open
them it stretches a bit more since I have like a lot of pieces to show you I'm going to switch
into the next one because it's pretty similar to this pants but in short these are the shorts
and I'm wearing super duper high heels and gold I have to film it like from the bottom to the top
because they're so high I'm not gonna fit in in the whole screen but I thought hey with these
short pants let's use the high heels and I think it's a nice combination as well
maybe not especially for Christmas because it's rather cold but for an
indoor Christmas party maybe I want to change into the next pants it's one with
buttons this time and we have this really really nice biker look detail
here in the leg and again the pockets in the back what's also cool with the
Chasse du Fils pants is that you have this anti slip rubber part in the pants
like on the inside so they don't slide down when you wear them I think these
are my favorite Chasse du Fils pants because of the biker style and the
The asymmetrical zippers which I really like because I love this design feature and also because they make my booty look really good which all of them do. But yeah I definitely do love the front design here. Also the anti slip down waistband here on the inside because they really cling to the body with that.
Also, the length of the pants is really good. I don't know if you can see it
My feet are not in the picture anymore
But they are really really long and I do not feel like I have to expose my ankles with these pants
But can be tall girl and have long trousers. I
Do have two catsuits now one with long legs and one with short legs
Yeah, this is it, so let's start
Thank you.
Okay, this is the short jumpsuit and don't mind my bruises because I just came home from
pole camp.
It is what it is.
Anyway I love the jumpsuits because I think they're an unusual design for jumpsuits and
And if you want to wear one piece rather than two separate pieces, this is the way to go.
But now I'm going to switch back into the top because I have two more leggings left.
And these are basically normal leggings without the fake pockets and without zippers and buttons.
So let's go.
one and I think the cut is more of a leisure wear leggings but the material is so yeah high quality
and thick that I would not wear this for sports because then I would sweat a lot and it's not
that stretchy as sport leggings are so you have a great really really comfy leggings that has
great fabric. I love that the waistline here has this cross kind of design
and overall super comfortable and now I'm going to the second leggings.
one last leggings it's the basic cut leggings and I think a bit more plain than all the zipper
pants so if that's a look then go for it and I'll link everything down in the description text
check out the shashka feet shop and leave a comment if you like what you saw if you already
have these kind of pants let me know how you find them give a thumbs up to this video and subscribe
to my channel and i will see you in the next video have a nice christmas if you buy these outfits for
christmas i want to see pictures of you wearing them underneath the christmas tree see you around
bye